Okay, it's time for a project. You have
made it. You have learned a lot about
coding. So, um, given a new hope opening
crawl text, I want you to create a new
HTML file. Insert the starter HTML.
Insert JavaScript. Create a variable
that contains the text of the opening
crawl. Find the position of the text
Civil War within that opening crawl.
Using that position, alert the text
Civil War. Grab it is and print it out
using your preferred method. Replace the
text of Galactic Empire with the name of
an evil organization of your choosing
and then alert the adjusted opening
crawl. And then I want to make sure that
you have commented your name at the top
and you've put a program description at
the top of your file. And then like any
good programmer, make sure you've used
clean comments throughout your code to
document your process. All right, good
luck.